adjetter.com 2012-02-20

# Adjetter | Privacy Policy

**What information does Adjetter Media Network gather and how is it used?**

  * Each time you visit the Site or use the Service, we may collect information about your visits, such as your Internet service provider, browser type, operating system, pages accessed on the Site or when using the Service, the date and time of access and other websites you access after visiting our Site. We use this information to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. We may also receive information telling us what site you linked from to get to the Site or the Service.
  * When you send us a message using the **Contact Us** page, we retain the content of the message, your email address, any information you may provide to us regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics (such as your name or age), experience with the Service, your contact preferences, and the response we send back to you. This helps us manage any follow-up questions you may have, measure how effectively we address your concerns and improve the Site and the Service. 
  * You may ask us to provide services or information to you by using an email address or telephone number which you may designate by sending us a message using the link provided on the Site. We will use the information you provide us to deliver the service or information. We may retain the content of your message, the email address, telephone number, and a record of the service or information provided. Any information retained would be used assure the delivery of the services or information you requested, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online.

If you provide us with an email address or telephone number, we may send you by email or text messages certain services, information or other messages related to your transactions with us or about our services. 

**Does Adjetter Media Network Conduct Online Surveys?**

We like feedback, which means we may conduct online surveys to solicit your opinions and comments. Participation in these surveys is of course optional. If you choose to participate, the information you provide will be aggregated with information from other users to make improvements to the user experience and develop appealing content, features and promotions. Unless otherwise noted in a survey, your participation will remain anonymous. 

**Does Adjetter Media Network have a feedback center?**

You can ask us questions on our website (www.Adjetter.com). You can also share comments or suggestions with us. Your questions, comments and suggestions may not be kept confidential. We may use your questions, comments and suggestions to improve the Site and the Service but we will have no obligation to compensate you for any such contributions. If you offer your name and address when you contact us, we'll be happy to respond directly to you.

**With whom does Adjetter Media Network share my personally identifiable information?**

We don't sell your name or other personally identifiable information to third parties. We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services.

We may use your IP address and share it with third parties to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage the Site and the Service, and to enhance the Site and the Service based on usage pattern data.

If we are acquired by another company, your personally identifiable information will be shared with our new owner, but it will remain subject to the terms of the then-applicable privacy policy or another set of terms if you agree to them. 

**How does Adjetter Media Network use cookies, tags, and similar technologies?**

We use cookies, tags and similar technologies to recognize your preferences and effectively and efficiently administer the Site. We use the information we collect to enhance your visit to the Site and provide you with information tailored to your interests.

You may elect to refuse cookies, however doing so may affect your use of some portions of the Services and our partners services.

We use third party tracking and advertising providers to act on our behalf. The third-party tracking and advertising technology that we use on the Site uses information derived from your visits to the Site to target advertising to the Site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on the Site and other sites. They may track and analyze your usage of the Site through the use of cookies, pixel tags, web beacons and similar technologies. They may collect and share with us usage information about visits to the Site and use of the Service. They also may measure and research the effectiveness of our advertisements, track page usage and paths followed during and after your use of the Site and the Service, help us target the ads on the Site, and track use of our ads and other links from marketing partners' sites to the Service. The information collected on our behalf does not contain your name, address, email address or any other personally identifiable information. To "opt-out," please email Target@adjetter.com with your Adjetter user name.

**Does Adjetter Media Network collect information from children under the age of 13?**

The Site and the Service are not intended for use by children under 13, and we don't knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from kids that age. If someone under 13 attempts to provide us with personally identifiable information, it will be rejected by the Site. If a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us by clicking here Contact Us page to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. 

**Does the Site contain links to other websites?**

Adjetter Media Network.com contains links to other sites not owned by us that may have different privacy practices from ours. We aren't responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy doesn't apply to information collected by those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. When you leave our Site or Service via a link to interact with a site not governed by our Privacy Policy, a new browser window will open.

**How is my personally identifiable information protected?**

To prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or improper use of your information, and to maintain data accuracy, we've established reasonable physical, electronic and managerial safeguards to protect the information we collect. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information, we can't be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.

**How should I contact Adjetter Media Network about my personally identifiable information?**

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personally identifiable information, please write to us at:

**Adjetter Media Network Pvt Ltd,**   
267, 2nd floor    
Amar Jyoti layout (Next to Embassy Golf Links)   
Koramangala Inner ring road,   
Domlur, Bangalore - 560071, India.
